VIDUSHI RAWAT

Technical Business Analyst

PERSONAL INFO

- 9009001159
- vidushi rawat92@yahoo.com
- Indore, Madhya Pradesh
- www.linkedin.com/in/vidush i-Rawat-21707a144/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Project Management

Expert

Channel Management

Intermediate

Operations Planning

Intermediate

Sales Enablement

Intermediate

Analytical Skills

Expert

SOFT SKILLS

Leadership

Communication

Collaboration

Time Management

Analyst with 5+ years of expertise in delivery through project management and coordinate activities across functions. I am proactive, take up initiatives to understand requirements, and assure deliveries as per timelines. I am thrilled to keep adding value, grow my skill set and utilize my technical knowledge and communication in all opportunities.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL PROCESS SPECIALIST INFOSYS, 2021 – 2022

- Enhanced service delivery, assured deadlines are met and achieved proactive coordination across senior leadership and teams
- Supported development of project status reports as needed
- Assisted in roadmap of business adaptation capabilities
- Organized and inferred insights from business process and technical documents
- Created dashboard for client and stakeholders and collaborated with the team on daily basis to share status
- Prioritized and identified business capabilities for adaptation to upgrade
- Reviewed release notes and patch fixes and provided business, technical, and configuration impact analysis
- Identified opportunities to add in sales revenue and created active working relationship with teams to enable targets achieving

BUSINESS COORDINATOR

BRINTON PHARMACEUTICALS Pvt. Ltd., 2017 – 2021

- Supported and coordinated teams across 32 countries for engagement management
- Inferred latest trends and drew insights of the focused market by tracking, and analyzing data from AWACS, SMSRC, and IQVIA.
- Conducted brainstorming sessions with product managers with sales team to understand challenges and growth opportunities to improve revenue
- Administered campaigns to raise conversion rates, analyze market penetration and troubleshoot challenges in incentive release of the end customer
- Prioritized and strengthened key performance indicators (KPI) of sales field, improved coordination of HO with the marketing team to assure team alignment and timely result

EDUCATION

MBA – Marketing and Finance ICFAI Business School, Hyderabad, Telangana

2015 - 2017

Bachelor of Technology – Electronics and Communication Banasthali Vidyapith, Newai, Rajasthan

2010 - 2014